Secretary of the Faculty for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Records UA037
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Faculty meeting minutes, 1854 -- 2019; UA037.001; 9.4 Linear Feet; 55 Volumes; 431 Digital Object(s); 938 Megabytes 429 of 431 digital objects comprise 938 megabytes.
  - CSS, 2005 -- 2007; UA037.001.076.00041 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2007 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00042 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2007 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00043 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2007 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00044 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2007 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00045 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2002 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00046 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2002 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00047 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2003 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00048 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2004 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00049 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2005 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00050 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2007 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00051 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2007 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00052 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2007 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00053 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2007 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00054 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2001 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00055 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2002 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00056 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2004 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00057 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00058 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00059 (Box 76)
  - Engineering, 2007 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00060 (Box 76)
  - Engineering, 2007 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00061 (Box 76)
  - Engineering [No Report], 2007 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00062 (Box 76)
  - Engineering, 2007 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00063 (Box 76)
  - Engineering, 2001 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00064 (Box 76)
  - Engineering [No Report], 2002 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00065 (Box 76)
  - Engineering [No Report], 2003 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00066 (Box 76)
  - Engineering [No Report], 2004 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00067 (Box 76)
  - Engineering [No Report], 2005 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00068 (Box 76)
  - Engineering, 2005 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00069 (Box 76)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2007 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00070 (Box 76)
  - College of Special Studies, 2007 -- 2008; UA037.001.076.00071 (Box 76)
  - Date and location list, 2008; UA037.001.076.00072 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, 2008; UA037.001.076.00073 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2008 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00074 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, 2008 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00075 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2008 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00076 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, 2008 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00077 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, 2008 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00078 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2008 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00079 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2001 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00080 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, 2002 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00081 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, 2002 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00082 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2003 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00083 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2003 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00084 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2004 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00085 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00086 (Box 76)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering, 2005 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00087 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00088 (Box 76)
  - College of Special Studies (CSS), 2008 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00089 (Box 76)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (GSAS), 2008 -- 2009; UA037.001.076.00090 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2009; UA037.001.076.00091 (Box 76)
    Degrees, Agenda, Meeting Minutes.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00092 (Box 76)
    Degrees, Agenda, Meeting Minutes, Appendix A Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix B College of Special Studies Degree Candidates; Appendix C Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix D Curriculum Committee Proposal.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2009 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00093 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Curriculum Committee Proposal.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2001 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00094 (Box 76)
    Cancelled.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2003 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00095 (Box 76)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2003 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00096 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Curriculum Committee Proposals; Appendix B School of Arts and Sciences Phased Retirement Program Summary; Appendix C Frequently Asked Questions and Answers.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00097 (Box 76)
    Degrees; Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A College of Special Studies Degree Candidates; Appendix B Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix C Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Apprendix D Curriculum Committee Proposals.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00098 (Box 76)
    Honors; Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Summa Honors Candidates.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2009; UA037.001.076.00099 (Box 76)
    Degrees; Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix B School of Engineering Degree Candidates, Bachelor and Graduate; Appendix C Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix D 2009-2010 New Faculty Biographies.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2009; UA037.001.076.00100 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2009 -- 2011; UA037.001.076.00101 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; appendix A Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix B School of Engineering Degree Candidates; Appendix C Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2009 -- 2012; UA037.001.076.00102 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A election Procedures for elected Standing Committees; Appendix B Report of Proposed Bylaw Change for the School of Engineering.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2002 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00103 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A Summa Honors Candidates; Appendix B Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix C College of Special Studies Degree Candidates; Appendix D Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix E School of Engineering Degree Candidates.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2002 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00104 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A Message from Executive Committee to Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2003 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00105 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A EPC Resolution on Course Evaluations; Appendix B Graduate Student Council Course Evaluation Feedback by Department (distribution online only); Appendix C Uniform course Evaluations (distributed online only); Appendix D TCU Senate Resolution to Support changing the Course Evaluation System (distributed online only); Appendix E TCU Senate Resolution to Oppose a Faculty opt-out policy for Course Evaluation (distribution online only).
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2004 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00106 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A EPC Resolution on Course Evaluations; Appendix B TCU Senate Resolution to Oppose a Faculty opt-out policy for Course Evaluations; Appendix C EPC Resolution on Veterans Day 2010; Appendix D TCU Senate Resolution to better integrate Veterans Day into Undergraduate Life; Appendix E AAUP Table Tufts Peer Institutions' Salaries by Rand and AAUP Ranking Scale.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2005 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00107 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; School of Engineering Degree Candidates.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2009; UA037.001.076.00108 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00109 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A Bylaws of the Faculty of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences; Appendix B Proposal School of Psychology; Appendix C Proposal School of Pyschology Appendices.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00110 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A Graduate School of Arts and ciences Degree Candidates.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2002 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00111 (Box 76)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2002 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00112 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A Proposal for new dual degrees.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00113 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree candidates.
  - College of Special Studies, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00114 (Box 76)
    Agenda; Meeting minutes; Appendix A College of Special Studies Degree Candidates.
  - College of Special Studies, 2002 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00115 (Box 76)
  - College of Special Studies, 2005 -- 2010; UA037.001.076.00116 (Box 76)
  - Executive committee engineering [packet] 1 of 3, 1919 -- 1929; UA037.001.079.00001 (Box 79)
  - Executive committee engineering [packet] 2 of 3, 1929 -- 1939; UA037.001.079.00002 (Box 79)
  - Executive committee engineering [packet] 3 of 3, 1939 -- 1958; UA037.001.079.00003 (Box 79)
  - Academic standing committee [packet] 1 of 3, 1930 -- 1936; UA037.001.079.00004 (Box 79)
  - Academic standing committee [packet] 2 of 3, 1936 -- 1945; UA037.001.079.00005 (Box 79)
  - Academic standing committee [packet] 3 of 3, 1945 -- 1951; UA037.001.079.00006 (Box 79)
  - Curriculum committee [packet] 1 of 1, 1909 -- 1918; UA037.001.079.00007 (Box 79)
  - Scholarship committee [packet] 1 of 1, 1914 -- 1918; UA037.001.079.00008 (Box 79)
  - Committee on administration [packet] 1 of 2, 1926 -- 1931; UA037.001.079.00009 (Box 79)
  - Committee on administration [packet] 2 of 2, 1931 -- 1940; UA037.001.079.00010 (Box 79)
  - A and S faculty [packet] 1 of 1, 1927 -- 1939; UA037.001.079.00011 (Box 79)
  - Engineering faculty minutes [packet] 1 of 5, 1903 -- 1912; UA037.001.079.00012 (Box 79)
  - Engineering faculty minutes [packet] 2 of 5, 1912 -- 1917; UA037.001.079.00013 (Box 79)
  - Engineering faculty minutes [packet] 3 of 5, 1917 -- 1923; UA037.001.079.00014 (Box 79)
  - Engineering faculty minutes [packet] 4 of 5, 1923 -- 1930; UA037.001.079.00015 (Box 79)
  - Engineering faculty minutes [packet] 5 of 5, 1931 -- 1939; UA037.001.079.00016 (Box 79)
  - Promotions committee [packet] 1 of 4, 1903 -- 1909; UA037.001.079.00017 (Box 79)
  - Promotions committee [packet] 2 of 4, 1909 -- 1913; UA037.001.079.00018 (Box 79)
  - Promotions committee [packet] 3 of 4, 1913 -- 1915; UA037.001.079.00019 (Box 79)
  - Promotions committee [packet] 4 of 4, 1915 -- 1919; UA037.001.079.00020 (Box 79)
  - Underclass committee [packet] 1 of 1, 1919 -- 1929; UA037.001.079.00021 (Box 79)
  - Upperclass committee [packet] 1 of 1, 1919 -- 1929; UA037.001.079.00022 (Box 79)
  - Action of committee on promotions and academic standing [binder] 1 of 3, 1911 -- 1936; UA037.001.079.00023 (Box 79)
  - Register of students [binder] 2 of 3, 1918 -- 1931; UA037.001.079.00024 (Box 79)
  - Register of students [binder] 3 of 3, 1928 -- 1936; UA037.001.079.00025 (Box 79)
  - Register of students [binder] 1 of 2, 1961 -- 1965; UA037.001.079.00026 (Box 79)
  - Register of students [binder] 2 of 2, 1961 -- 1965; UA037.001.079.00027 (Box 79)
  - Tenure and promotion, F.C. Nelson [binder] 1 of 1, 1971 -- 1972; UA037.001.079.00028 (Box 79)
  - Tufts University faculty handbook [binder] 1 of 1, 1970; UA037.001.079.00029 (Box 79)
  - Alphabetical Index to Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1960 -- 1988; UA037.001.080.00001
    20 years from date of creation.
  - Faculty Meeting Indices, 1987 -- 2006; UA037.001.080.00002
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.081.00001 (Box 81)
    Degrees; Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix B Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix C College of Special Studies Degree Candidates; Appendix D School of Engineering Degree Candidates, Bachelor and Graduate; 2010-2011 New Faculty Biographies.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.081.00002 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Work/Life Balance Force Charge; Appendix B Next Generation LMS Strategy Recommendations.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2010; UA037.001.081.00003 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix B School of Engineering Degree Candidates; Appendix C Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix D EPC Resolution on Student Course Evaluations; Appendix E Tufts Course Evaluation Process (Presentation); Appendix F Procedures at Other Universities for handling grievances involving alleged discrimination; Appendix G Investigation on discrimination complains to University Administration.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2010 -- 2012; UA037.001.081.00004 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Grievance Panel Procedures Presentation; Appendix B Tufts Faculty Handbook for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Chapter 5 Appeals and Grievances; Appendix C Tufts Faculty Handbook for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Chapter 5 Appeals and Grienvances Notated with Proposed changes; Appendix D Rationale for Proposed changes to grievance panel procedure; Appendix E Discussion points concerning potential revisions to the grievance panel procedures as outilines in Chapter 5 of the AS and E Faculty Handbook.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2002 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00005 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A College of Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix B Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix C School of Engineering Degree Candidates; Appendix D School of Engineering Graduate Degree Candidates; Appendix E EPC Discussion on changes to Course Evaluation Procedure.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2003 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00006 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Election Ballows 2011-2012; Appendix B Proposed changest to Athletics Committee Bylaws; Appendix C Search Committee for Director of Tisch Library.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2003 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00007 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Proposed changes in grievance panel procedures; Appendix B Rationale for changes to grievance panel procedures; Appendix C Current Grievance panel procedures; Appendix D Proposed changes to Athletics Committee Bylaws; Appendix E Resolution on the Recording of ROTC participation on Tufts Transcripts; Apprendix F Proposed Joint Ph.D. in Cognitive Science.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2004 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00008 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Proposed changes in grievance panel procedures; Appendix B ROTC Resolution revised.
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering, 2005 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00009 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A College of Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix B Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix C School of Engineering Degree Candidates; Appendix D School of Engineering Graduate Degree Candidates.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.081.00010 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2010; UA037.001.081.00011 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix B College of Speical Studies Degree Candidates; Appendix C Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix D Curriculum Committee Proposal.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2010 -- 2012; UA037.001.081.00012 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Curriculum Committee Proposals.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2002 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00013 (Box 81)
    Degrees and Honors; Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Dean's Humanities Fellowship; Appendix B Seed Grants for Teaching and Research; Appendix C Seed Grants Program Proposal Submission Form; Appendix D Liberal Arts and Jackson College Summa Honors Candidates; Appendix E Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix F College of Speical Studies Degree Candidates; Appendix G Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2003 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00014 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Curriculum Committee Proposals
  - Arts and Sciences, 2004 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00015 (Box 81)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00016 (Box 81)
    Degrees; Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A College of Special Studies Degree Candidates; Appendix B Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates; Appendix C Liberal Arts and Jackson College Degree Candidates; Appendix D Curricula Committee Proposals.
  - Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00017 (Box 81)
    Honors; Agenda; Meeting Minutes.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.081.00018 (Box 81)
    Degree; Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2010; UA037.001.081.00019 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Proposed Certificate in Science Education; Appendix B Presentation on NRC Assessment; Appendix C Proposal for Teaching and Research Assistant.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2010; UA037.001.081.00020 (Box 81)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2002 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00021 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2002 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00022 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Proposal and vote for a chemical physics track in the Ph.D. program for Chemistry and Physics and Astronomy Departments; Appendix B Teaching and Research Assistant Assessment.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2003 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00023 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A Proposal for a Joint Ph.D. in cognitive Science at Tufts.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2005 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00024 (Box 81)
    Degrees; Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Degree Candidates.
  - College of Special Studies, 2009 -- 2010; UA037.001.081.00025 (Box 81)
    Agenda; Meeting Minutes; Appendix A College of Speical Studies Degree Candidates.
  - College of Special Studies, 2010; UA037.001.081.00026 (Box 81)
  - College of Special Studies, 2002 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00027 (Box 81)
  - College of Special Studies, 2005 -- 2011; UA037.001.081.00028 (Box 81)
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00029 (Box 81)
    LA and J Degree Candidates; GSAS Degree Candidates; CSS Degree Candidates; Eng Degree Candidates; B and P Special Ballot; New Faculty Bios
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00030 (Box 81)
    New Research Conflict Interest Policies
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00031 (Box 81)
    GSAS Degree Candidates; LA and J Committee Proposals; Council on Diversity
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00032 (Box 81)
    LA and J Curricula Committee Proposals; Summary of Proposed LA and J Bylaw Changes; Draft LA and J Bylaws with mark-up and with changes
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00033 (Box 81)
    LA and J Degree Candidates; GSAS Degree Candidates; CSS Degree Candidates; Honors Candidates; Summary of Proposed LA and J Bylaw changes; Draft LA and J bylaws (with mark-ups); Draft LA and J Bylaws (with changes)
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00034 (Box 81)
    LA and J Curricula Committee Proposals; TEAM FAQ; Tufts CTSI
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00035 (Box 81)
    Reasearch Leave Program (draft); LA and J Curricula Committee Proposals; iSIS Training
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00036 (Box 81)
    Faculty Retreat Invitation; LA and J Degree Candidates; GSAS Degree Candidates; CSS Degree Candidates; LA and J Information regarding ASLProposal; Pre-Major Advising Document
  - Arts and Science Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00037 (Box 81)
    Honors document
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00038 (Box 81)
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00039 (Box 81)
    Talloires Announcement; Talloires flyer; B and P Special Election Ballot; Academic calendar
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00040 (Box 81)
    LA and J Degree Candidates; Eng Degree candidates; GSAS degree candidates; Student course evaluations plans, 2012-2013; Administrations' Interim Response to Report from Task Force on Work/Life Balance
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012; UA037.001.081.00041 (Box 81)
    Minors Policy, executive summary
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00042 (Box 81)
    LA and J Degree Candidates; Eng Degree Candidates; GSAS Degree candidates; Tufts Inovations Institute Draft Document
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00043 (Box 81)
    Relay for Life; Nominations summary
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00044 (Box 81)
    Proposal for new online course evaluation
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00045 (Box 81)
    Diversity Council Report
  - Arts, Sciences, and Engineering Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2013; UA037.001.081.00046 (Box 81)
    LA and J Degree Candidates; Eng Degree Candidates; GSAS Degree Candidates; Eng Graduate Degree Candidates; Briefing Materials
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012 -- 2013; UA037.001.081.00047 (Box 81)
    Degree candidates and proposed dual degree program
  - College of Special Studies Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2012 -- 2013; UA037.001.081.00048 (Box 81)
    Special Studies degree candidates
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, Spring 2014; UA037.001105; 3.4 Megabytes; 5 Digital Object(s)
    - Department chairs meeting agenda, 2014 January 14; UA037.001106; 121.7 Kilobytes
    - Department chair guidelines for recognition of retiring full-time faculty members, 2014 January 14; UA037.001107; 115.3 Kilobytes
    - Department chair meeting presentation, 2014 January 14; UA037.001108; 3 Megabytes
    - Guidelines for assigning credit hours to courses, 2014 January 14; UA037.001109; 180.2 Kilobytes
    - Proposal on credit unit for Educational Policy Committee, Spring 2015, 2014 January 14; UA037.001110; 92.3 Kilobytes
  - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting agendas, minutes, and attachments, 2014 -- 2015; UA037.001111; 35 Megabytes; 48 Digital Object(s)
    - Arts and Sciences faculty meeting minutes, 2014 September 10; UA037.001112; 227.9 Kilobytes
    - Arts and Sciences working goals, 2014 September 10; UA037.001113; 114 Kilobytes
    - Department chairs meeting agenda, 2014 October 01; UA037.001114; 108.1 Kilobytes